你真的可以给Hammersmith用胡萝卜
You could use carrots for Hammersmith really
非常
你懂
You know
完成了
There was complete
Ok Homes Perth
Ok homes Perth
我可以剪掉顶部吗
Can I cut the top off
我的手指
My finger
TUI网站
TUI site
胡萝卜已经是什么了
What are them by the carrot already
听起来不错
Sounds good
像这样
Like this
兵工厂
Arsenal
第一次制作开始到最后
First take office starts on the end
你想脱皮吗
Do you want to take the peel off
部分占三分之二
Is parties in thirds
您希望它们足够坚固以至于
You want them to be strong enough to let
将锤子移向脸部
Move the Hammers towards the face
我只是在稍稍被诊断为可以
I'm just running slightly diagnosed that you can x
对你更诚实
Get more honest on you
前往那里
Heading up in there
看看那个
Just look at that
这就是他听到的
This is what he was hearing
所以我要先去皮
So I'm going to peel this first
胡萝卜比较稀吗
Does a relatively thin carrots so
我喜欢做我正在做的蔬菜
I like to do what I'm doing with the vegetable this is
根据尺寸直接装入可管理的尺寸块
Carried into manageable size pieces based on the size so straight down
所以我要把它切成两半
So through and I'm Gonna Cut that in half
直到最后
And even
完美的胡萝卜
The perfect carrots